(Sheldon:)If it were a game,
here are your choices.
(Sheldon:)An e-mail from an old acquaintance...
(Sheldon:)...or the head of one of the largest
religious institutions in the world...
...slam-dunking
to "Sweet Georgia Brown." Pick.
(Leonard:)Just do it,
because he's not gonna let it go.
- Basketball Pope.
- And that's how it's done.
What are you gonna do?
(Penny:)- Are you gonna see him?
- I don't know.
(Sheldon:)Is this the fellow who peed
in your Hawaiian Punch?
(Leonard:)No, that was a different guy.
(Sheldon:)Was he the one who wedgied you
so hard your testicle reascended...
(Sheldon:)...and you spent your whole Christmas
break waiting for it to come back down?
(Leonard:)No, that was a different different guy.
(Sheldon:)Was he the one who used your head
to open a nut?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Oh, oh, oh.
(Sheldon:)Was he the one
who made you eat your arm hair?
(Leonard:)No, but actually,
that was this guy's sister.
(Penny:)- Well, what do you think he wants?
- I don't know.
(Sheldon:)The holidays
are just around the corner.
(Sheldon:)Maybe he wants to see if he can lodge
the other testicle up there.
(Leonard:)I told you. That was a different guy.
Mm, that's too bad. Could've spent New
Year's Eve waiting for the ball to drop.